Guide to the Everett Needham Case papers A1015
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
Everett Needham Case papers
1913-1982
A1015
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
10.0 Cubic feet
Case, Everett Needham
Access to Collection
Collection is open for research.
Related Archival Materials note
For more information about Case's involvement in the Milkshed Committee see: A1031, Milkshed Committee collection, Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries.
Case, Josephine Young, 1907-1990; Colgate University--Presidents.
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas Hale., 1940 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Editor, VHS Highlights., 1940 February 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dale Warren., 1940 February 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James M. Landis., 1940 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David Luke., 1940 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Caroline Phillips Smith., 1940 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George L. Harrison., 1940 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Hemenway, Jr., 1940 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Carter., 1940 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Samuel Carter., 1940 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J. Edward Todd., 1940 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Wendell Andrews., 1940 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1940 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Halsey., 1940 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 June 21 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald Brush., 1940 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Albert Sauveur., 1940 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Hofer., 1940 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Caroline Phillips Smith., 1940 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Will D. Howe., 1940 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Maguire., 1940 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Joseph Lichty., 1940 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mae Harrod., 1940 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Margaret Egan., 1940 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Will D. Howe., 1940 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.P.G. Fuller., 1940 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Hard., 1940 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Will D. Howe., 1940 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Hager., 1940 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.P.G. Fuller., 1940 September 17 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Elwood., 1940 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.P.G. Fuller., 1940 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Hard., 1940 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1940 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Hard., 1940 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fred Gowen., 1940 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Hard., 1940 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Maguire., 1940 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter Edmonds., 1946 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: G. Denny Hynes., 1946 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Arthur G. Poor., 1946 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Faith Young., 1946 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H. Alexander Smith., 1946 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Russell Porter., 1946 April 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Homer Cochran., 1946 March 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mary Downs., 1946 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter, Jr., 1946 March 16 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fritz Foord., 1946 March 30 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fannie Mann., 1946 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Ruth Fuller., 1946 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mary Peyton., 1946 June 14 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Winter., 1946 June 20 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mary H. Dearing., 1946 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mary Day., 1946 June 27 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David Dorin., 1946 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Raymond Hall., 1947 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Radcliffe Heermance., 1947 February 10 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: E.J. Dimock., 1947 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas H. Carroll., 1947 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Lawrence Terry., 1947 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Webster Todd., 1948 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Young., 1948 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas J. Watson., 1948 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Stevens., 1948 September 3 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J. Herbert Gabelain., 1948 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Guy Emerson., 1948 September 8 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Stevens., 1948 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Martin Eagan., 1948 September 24 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1948 October 5 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter Edmonds., 1949 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Martin Eagan., 1949 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Gertrude Chandler., 1949 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Peter Edmonds., 1949 April 14 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Lindsay Bradford., 1949 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald David., 1949 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Bingham., 1949 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald Hall., 1949 July 2 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1949 July 2 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter Teagle., 1949 October 5 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Rufus H. Fitzgerald., 1949 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Avirett., 1949 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1949 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Jessup., 1949 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Joseph Lichty., 1949 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Telegram. Case, Everett N. To: Adlai Stevenson., 1949 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Avirett., 1949 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Alan Valentine., 1949 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald Lourie., 1949 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Mason., 1949 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1949 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Riddle., 1949 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Sally Nichols., 1949 December 20 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Van Santvoord., 1949 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Gerard Swope., 1949 December 29 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1946 March 13 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1947 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1947 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1947 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1947 September 26 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1947 December 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1947 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1948 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1948 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Samuel Stratton., 1948 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1948 January 28 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Telegram. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1948 March 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Telegram. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1948 March 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1948 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1948 November 15 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1948 November 16 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1948 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- TN, initialed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1948 December 19 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- TN, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1948 December 29 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Josephine Case., 1949 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1949 January 17 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1949 February 16 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1949 April 7 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1949 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Walter Teagle., 1949 July 29 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- TL, signed. Valentine, Alan. To: Owen D. Young., 1949 November 25 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: James Conant., 1950 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, J.H. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 March 22 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Telegram. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1950 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- AL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1950 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1950 May 23 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- TL, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 May 25 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 September 19 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1950 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1950 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1950 December 30 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1951 January 3 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1951 January 13 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1951 January 26 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1951 November 9 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1952 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- TN, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1952 March 26 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- TN, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1952 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- TN, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1952 September 22 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1952 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Oliver Carmichael., 1952 November 3 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Oliver Carmichael., 1952 November 6 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1952 November 16 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1952 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1952 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: John Foster Dulles., 1952 November 25 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1952 November 26 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1952 November 26 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1952 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1952 December 29 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1953 January 26 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1953 April 21 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- TN, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1953 May 8 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- TN, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1953 October 28 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- TN, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1953 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1954 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1954 April 12 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1954 September 26 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1954 September 28 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1954 December 29 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1955 February 16 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. J.H. Case., 1945 July 31 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. J.H. Case., 1945 October 5 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1945 October 30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. J.H. Case., 1945 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- TL, unsinged. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. J.H. Case., 1945 December 21 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Betty Case., 1948 April 16 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1949 September 30 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1949 October 3 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1949 December 10 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1949 December 15 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1950 April 18 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. J.H. Case., 1950 June 7 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1950 November 30 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- TN, unsigned. Csae, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1950 December 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1951 March 27 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1951 July 11 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. J.H. Case., 1951 October 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. J.H. Case., 1951 October 29 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- TL, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. J.H. Case., 1951 November 29 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Young., 1951 January 13 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Deane Malott., 1951 January 16 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Sargeant Ackerson., 1951 January 26 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Salvatore Pirro., 1951 February 15 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Hollingshead., 1951 March 22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Whitton., 1951 April 11 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: W. Randolph Burgess., 1951 April 20 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1951 April 27 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Marcel Chesebro., 1951 May 14 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip David., 1951 May 29 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Frost., 1951 June 12 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1951 June 12 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. S. Arthur Devan., 1951 June 12 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louise Rice., 1951 July 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1951 July 11 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.P.G. Fuller., 1951 July 30 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Pulling., 1951 July 30 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter Teagle., 1951 July 30 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. Deane Malott., 1951 September 10 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To; George Harrison., 1951 October 23 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Kennan., 1951 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Cleveland Chase., 1951 November 27 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Christian Gauss., 1951 November 30 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1951 December 21 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Alan Valentine., 1951 December 28 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: A. Glen Acheson., 1952 January 7 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Brent., 1952 January 31 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Deane Malott., 1952 February 4 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1952 February 6 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Barkie Henry., 1952 February 7 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frederick Foord., 1952 February 12 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David McCord., 1952 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald Hall., 1952 June 17 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Hofer., 1952 June 18 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett. N. To: Walter Edmonds., 1952 July 8 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1952 September 25 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Diana Pershouse., 1952 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.Y. Simpson., 1952 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Elwood., 1952 October 3 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Roberts., 1952 November 7 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Irving Ives., 1952 November 7 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Sollace Mitchell., 1952 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Hagerty., 1952 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Read., 1952 December 19 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.P. Stevens., 1952 December 20 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Stevens., 1952 December 20 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Nason., 1952 December 20 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Stanley King., 1952 December 20 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Marquis Childs., 1952 December 22 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Whipple., 1952 December 22 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald Lourie., 1953 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde., 1953 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: "Margaret.", 1953 February 6 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Douglas., 1953 February 24 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Marshall Best., 1953 April 3 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: R.M. Cheseldine., 1953 April 3 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Henry Wriston., 1953 May 25 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Theodore Greene., 1953 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Harry Newburn., 1953 June 30 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Emerson., 1953 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Scott Fletcher., 1953 June 11 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Arthur Cotins., 1953 July 7 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John foster Dulles., 1953 July 7 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Weeks., 1953 November 3 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Harry Truman., 1953 November 17 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Alan Valentine., 1953 December 18 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- AL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1941 April 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Testimony on Milk. Young, Owen D. Albany, N.Y., 1941 August 8 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Radio speech. Young, Owen D., 1941 September 5 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1941 October 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1941 October 9 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1941 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1941 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1940 January 18 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1940 May 3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Roosevelt, Franklin D. To: Owen D. Young., 1940 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Harry Hopkins., 1940 May 27 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Franklin Roosevelt., 1940 May 27 (Box 6, Folder 13)